[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "More than 2000 years ago this famous philosopher and founder of medicine stated that The way to health is an aromatic bath and scented oils massage every day.", "correct_answer": "Hippocrates", "incorrect_answers": ["Homer", "Anaximander", "Pythagoras"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Mr. Jones eating in the movie Friday when he catches Craig in the refrigerator?", "correct_answer": "Grapes", "incorrect_answers": ["Pig Feet", "A Hot Dog", "Nothing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who claims to be a virgin in the movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "Gloria Cleary", "incorrect_answers": ["Christina Cleary", "Kathleen Cleary", "Clair Cleary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old was recent college graduate Benjamin at the beginning of The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "20", "incorrect_answers": ["22", "23", "25"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Katt starred in this 1980s movie with George Wendt of Cheers fame.", "correct_answer": "House", "incorrect_answers": ["The Toxic Avenger", "Evil Dead", "Reanimator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The atoms of which type of chemical elements have a complete set of valence electrons - 8?", "correct_answer": "Noble gases", "incorrect_answers": ["Chlorides", "Salts", "Alkali metals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Mediterranean Sea is connected to the Atlantic Ocean by this strait.", "correct_answer": "The Strait of Gibraltar", "incorrect_answers": ["The Dardanelles", "Strait of Magellan", "Strait of Dover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main ingredient of the popular French dessert Teurgoule?", "correct_answer": "Rice", "incorrect_answers": ["Eggs", "Potatoes", "Apples"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Troops who are likely to be attacked with chemical weapons often carry auto-injectors with this substance.", "correct_answer": "Atropine", "incorrect_answers": ["Solanine", "Digoxin", "Digitoxin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie is Casablanca . He said, Heres looking at you, kid . What did she say?", "correct_answer": "Play it, Sam. Play As Time Goes By.", "incorrect_answers": ["Of all the gin joints, in all the towns, in all the world, he had to be here.", "Well always have Paris.", "Play it again, Sam."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Saturday Night Fever, Tony Manero and his friends from Bay Ridge, Brooklyn, climbed along the parapets of which bridge?", "correct_answer": "Verrazano Narrows Bridge", "incorrect_answers": ["Triboro Bridge", "Manhattan Bridge", "Brooklyn Bridge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Burmese variation of chess known as?", "correct_answer": "Sittuyin", "incorrect_answers": ["mylangin", "masala", "kyoki"]}]